Skilled technician proficient in supporting hardware and software issues for Windows computer systems. Specializing in troubleshooting Dell and Lenovo products. Desiring to gain an entry-level position in network or system administration, increasing knowledge level in system support tools such as: Veeam, Solarwinds etc.

## **Work History**

2020-04 -Current

#### **Field Service Technician**

Papertec Inc., Longview, WA

- Maintained high speed camera system for the paper industry.
- Provided monthly report of system status to customers.
- Installed new cameras, server equipment and trained users on operation.
- Supported multiple client locations covering: Washington and Oregon.
- Ordered all replacement parts and managed inventory.
- Performed system troubleshooting to determine problems.
- Made recommendations regarding infrastructure overhauls.

2020-03 -2020-08

#### IT Field Technician

Philips Healthcare (Peak), Longview, WA

- Performed troubleshooting and diagnostics of malfunctioning equipment, machinery, tools and components.
- Installed and updated software for IntelliVue and SureSigns medical equipment on clients' premises.
   Calibrating devices for optimal performance.
- Performed service visits and completed preventative maintenance on all systems.
- Kept detailed records of field measurements and data.

2017-11 -2019-10

## Support Technician 1

Sea Mar Community Health Centers, Vancouver, WA

Provided solutions to operations issues for users of

# Jason Crosswhite

Skilled IT Technician

#### Contact

**Address** 

Longview, WA, 98632

**Phone** 

360-560-8057

E-mail

JasonCrosswhite@outlook.c om

#### **Skills**

Windows Server Administration

**VMware** 

Desktop Support

Software testing

Field support

**User Training** 

Distribution: SCCM, PDQ
Deploy

**Active Directory** 

Feeling Stupid

Windows and Medical software, working closely via phone, email, live chat and web teleconference with end users.

- Supported 2500+ end-users covering 85+ locations, utilizing Active Directory and exchange/Office 365.
- Performed data center maintenance, running network cable and racking servers. Documenting network runs.
- Configured hardware, devices and software to set up work stations for employees.
- Analyzed business printer issues to identify troubleshooting methods needed for quick remediation. Removing and replacing malfunctioning components to correct hardware problems.
- Planned and implemented secondary power measures to safeguard vital business data.

### 2016-03 - Field Service Technician

Papertech Inc, Longview, WA

- Maintained high speed camera system for the paper industry.
  - Provided monthly report of system status to customers.
  - Installed new cameras, server equipment and trained users on operation.
  - Supported multiple client locations covering: Washington and Oregon.
  - Ordered all replacement parts and managed inventory.
  - Performed system troubleshooting to determine problems.
  - Made recommendations regarding infrastructure overhauls.

## 2015-11 - IT Technician II (IMAC)

Nike Inc (NSC Global), Beaverton, OR

- Performed asset maintenance for company equipment.
- Supported 4000+ end-users.
- Deployed Lenovo and HP computer hardware, configured and software on work stations for staff.

#### 2016-03 -2017-09

2016-03

- Patched software and installed new versions to eliminate security problems and protect data.
- Utilized data backups via Crash Plan.

#### **Education**

2007-09 - **GED** 

2008-01 Lower Columbia College - Longview, WA

#### **Certifications**

2015-03 Comptia: A+, Network+, Security+.

2020-07 VMware: VCP - Data Center Virtualization

Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA) (In Progress)

EC-Councle - Certified Ethical Hacker (In Progress)

#### **References**

Chris Blair 360-270-3800

Brenda Newton 360-952-2386 Colleen Hockaday 360-560-3854